and we'll go over the records together.
Me and Mom's City Council for Tuesday, May 20th,
won't be 25.
We'll begin with the personal chances.
We have none.
Three, going to the list.
Motion to approve.
Second.
I.
E.
John.
I.
Barnes.
Parker.
I.
Four.
Klein's list for Bans.
Arthur.
Most to approve.
Second.
I.
John.
Barnes.
I.
Parker.
I'm staying.
Five minutes from the April 15th, 205,
regular meeting in the May 1st, 205,
special meeting.
Motion to approve.
Second.
Hi.
E.
John.
I.
Five.
Six.
Budget amendment.
Number.
25.
That's 22.
For the MCV.
For version.
279.
That's.
And.
Number.
25.
That's.
11.
Because no longer needed.
Sports using $1,400 to $61.
That's.
Number 120.
Part.
And recreation fund.
Carry over.
To cover the 50,000.
Our payment.
To the boys and girls.
Good.
Semitary.
Receiving.
Expanding.
$700.
Of the open.
Of.
Transportation.
So it's doing three things.
And again.
If money is moving from.
That's.
That's a council job.
Or if the budget's.
Changing.
Anyway, growing.
Um.
So they.
We got more revenues.
And now they have a bigger expenditure.
That's a.
Function.
And that's.
We're doing all these things.
We're transferring money.
Um.
The CVB had some personnel changes.
They had done an amendment back in November.
That amendments no longer needed.
So I'm.
Um.
Sports is using.
Some carry over to.
Complete the payment to the boys and girls club.
To run.
The.
And then the cemetery got a grant that they're receiving in and expanding for $700.
Second.
Hi.
Seven.
Some.
Regarding the homeless population.
And my local homeless.
Rick.
Good evening.
I appreciate the opportunity to come in and talk about our.
Our streets that is in population.
Um.
Bear with me.
I don't.
Like the term.
Um.
Because they do have a home.
I have to be on a street.
That's why I call them street citizens.
So if you bear with me.
If I don't use the term homeless.
Um.
I do have a couple of guests that.
I'm going to have one.
I'm going to come up and.
And speak here in just a minute.
But most of the people in here in the room know who I am and know what I do.
If you don't, I guess that's possible.
We have been working very hard with our streets that is population now for a few years.
As you know, anytime we get cold weather or extreme hot weather, I'm on the phone bug in the
mayor for a building to set up a shelter to get people off the streets either because
it's too cold or too hot.
And we've been blessed, didn't mean it that way.
But we have been blessed that we've been able to get a building here and there not the last
one.
It was probably not the best facility to use because of location, but it actually turned out
to be the best facility to use because of the location.
It brought to light an awful lot of things being on Main Street.
And with that before I go any further, I'd like to introduce Chris real quick.
Chris, if you want to come up and say what you had to say if you had appreciated.
Chris, need a little street ministry, I go around and talk with the street citizens up down the
alleys and streets and the arts and things.
I've been doing it for 10 or 12 hours.
I used to take it out to a whole bunch of people and I was part of a few years ago, never in my
wildest dreams.
I'd be next to anyone, I'm homeless, but here I am, but I don't think the city really
puts it into the homeless.
We really, really need some place for people to go, there's six, six people out there
that need a place to go.
We really need some kind of a shelter.
It's, every day I'm seeing more and more and more people coming into town and I'm seeing 16,
18, 20-year-olds coming into town.
We really need some kind of shelter or something for the citizens.
I've several people in here, I've seen you have stopped and passed out a lot of things.
It seems like when I need something for somebody out on the street, I call it Rickaholark,
Frank, somebody finds what I need and I do appreciate everybody here that has helped in the past.
There is a need for a facility, as Mayor knows and as other people in the room know, we've
been working very hard to find the right location in the right kind of facility.
What we don't want, I guess I'll change the terminology a little bit, is we don't want a shelter
to speak.
And we're not going to be giving handouts, we're going to be giving hand-ups and I'm just going
to talk a little bit about the last shelter we had on Main Street because each and every
one of them we've done, we've had some amazing stories come out of.
Frank and I, this is Frank.
Please, nobody turn them in nice.
He's legit.
We probably go over and above to take care of our folks on a street.
We worked 24 or 36, 48 hours at a clip in that shelter.
And our goal was to one, to personally know each and every one of the people that were in that shelter.
And let them know that there's people out there that care.
There's a stigma with people living on a street.
You'll agree and you'll disagree.
But a lot of times people see people on a street.
Oh, they're a drug addict.
Oh, they steal.
Oh, they're got mental health problems.
And those are the first things that pop into people's heads.
And they are the old at their scream dad, their custat.
Very degraded.
And I would challenge anybody in here.
Take a week and step into their shoes and see what it's like.
The shelter that we set up on Main Street as we said probably not the most ideal location.
But it was ideal.
A lot of people got noticed and a lot of people stopped wanting to know what we're doing.
And how we were doing a lot of people.
I didn't realize this was such a problem.
I didn't realize that there's so many people on a street.
And we had maybe one time 50 people in here that's it.
We do have a very large street city or street citizen population here.
And I think I'm probably preaching the choir at most of you folks.
But the one thing that happened out of that, we were able to get people identification cards.
Well, okay, what's the big deal with an ID?
Right now, people don't have an ID.
They don't have an ID.
They get stopped.
I don't have an ID.
What happens?
They try to get a job.
Don't have an ID.
What happens?
A lot of other things.
I talked to Kelly earlier, trying to get a library book from the library.
As some of our folks try to do.
Can't get a library book because they can't get a library card.
They don't have a permanent address.
So they don't have an ID.
I think we have a fix on that.
We're going to check with the legal folks.
But we pretty much dedicated our time to try to one, bring awareness of the folks that not everybody's bad.
That lives on a street.
And I'll tell you that a lot of the video that I've been seeing people post in about people,
break it into cars and in the homes.
They're not people that live on the street.
And I can't wait to catch some of them so that maybe parents are going to realize your little snod is not as good as what you think he is.
But stop my job.
My job is to try to educate everybody on our problem and it is a problem.
And talking to the...
Lieutenant Governor about it, he said,
well, I don't see your homeless population as he called it.
Any worse than Oklahoma City or Tulsa.
He said, on the contrary, if you look at Per capita,
you're going to find we have a significantly high population.
And all by the way, those other places don't
have three states that border.
Which means they all know about our drug law.
Thank God we passed that drug law, right?
But we get people from Kansas, Missouri and Arkansas
across the border because they can get the cheap drug.
Number one, number two, I'm not going to get very much
trouble for talking around 900 pounds of pot.
Exaggerated a little bit, but still my point being
is we get an awful lot of people.
Young man, sit here in the middle.
Just let people know where you're from.
Broken arrow.
He came to us courtesy of the Tulsa Crisis Center,
drove him up here and dropped them off in my Emma and said,
my Emma will take care of you.
I think Tulsa probably has a lot more resources than we do.
But took the time to drive him up here.
We're taking care of him.
But through Chris, he's got ID card, he's got identification.
And oh, by the way, if we started that job, you hit?
So he's got a job.
Job in police department, dropping them off.
Tell him we go to my Emma because we have lots of
resources to take care of you there.
And it's funny sometimes we can tell who's coming from
job for just by the way they pack.
Believe it or not.
That's how much attention we've paid to a lot of our folks.
So how do we do?
How can we fix this?
Well, you've heard about facility.
And that one we had in January, February.
We had people to got jobs.
We got ID cards.
We got birth certificates.
We got driver's license.
We took the time to get to know each and every person
and what their need was.
And sorry.
We got people to rehab.
Which is probably the biggest thing.
One young man, four years, we've been fighting to get him to rehab.
He's always refused or he's gone and quit.
He graduated a couple of weeks ago.
And he's married.
And he's got to have a testimony.
The testimony comes back.
He's not going to come back to live.
He knows his day away from my Emma now.
But he does want to come back and just tell people his story.
So it can be done with the right people.
Take time and sit down and talk.
Get to know people.
It's amazing.
what you'll find out. You'll find out how much talent a lot of people have. Yeah, a lot of people
do have some mental health problems. But again, that can be fixed. We can help those people.
People that are committing crime. Yeah. We're going to get caught and they'll do their time.
But rest assured, a lot of them are not living on the street. How are we going to get there? We need a building.
We've been searching hard for a building. We've got three prospects right now
that possibilities. I just want to let people know that we're not going to run our shelter. It's not going to be a shelter.
It's not going to be a flop house. It's going to be a place where they can go to eat.
Get things that they need to get their life back together. All the way through job and hopefully housing and whatever the case may be.
So, I just wanted to bring attention tonight that our numbers are growing.
We break it high and Chris, especially he's on the street. He cruises the street quite a bit.
We cruise the streets quite a bit and we're seeing an awful lot of new phases.
Last month, the third Saturday of each month, we got a spot here in town. We pull up and we cook for folks on the street.
Last Saturday of the month. The first time we did this, we served 62 people in 90% of those were people we'd never seen before.
Some are just passing through. A lot of people aren't passing through. They're stopping and staying here.
We need to help. I'm sure many of you are Christians. A lot of times that our Christian walk, we forget who Jesus served.
Wasn't the rich, wasn't the Lord's and everybody else like that. Jesus served. Those that were poor.
In fact, he charters. Read the Bible. It says right in here, what we are supposed to do, who is supposed to serve.
And a lot of times we turn our head, they're panhandling. I'll only want some money for drugs. Some do. Not going to debate that.
But we can get those people in a rehabilitation if we work it. I will tell you that if two of us can do everything that we did in those close to the 60 days, imagine what we could do if we have a building that's open every single day.
That can provide the services one stop for these folks. They don't have to walk all over the city to try to get an ID card, try to get a driver's license, try to get a birth certificate, et cetera.
And that's what we can do. So I'm not going to take up much more of your time. I appreciate the opportunity to come and talk to you folks about this.
We're trying to work on ourselves.
So if there's a facility out there that somebody knows about the Tempty that's of good size and not in major repair
We know we got to do some repairs in some of our places. We're happy to do that
We just need an opportunity to help our folks and I'll just echo a little bit with Chris said
This county and especially the city is probably one of the most giving cities. I've ever been in
We have never had a shelter operation or any kind of operation
Where if a call went out for something people didn't deliver we have some of the most carrying people around in the city
We want to draw on that we want to help people help people the right way
Thank you. I want to say thank you and a little bit more than
80% of the homeless that are here are not bad people. I can promise you that most of our criminals are
Are not from the homeless that they're not and I've seen it all you know what I do and I see it and
Most of them are not homeless
Thank you, really I think
Good evening as always it's a pleasure to be here before the council
I'm going to be believe it or not brief. That's your channel
I
Three things I want to quickly tell you about number one. We told you recently. Obviously. We released our housing study
For my amon auto a county and I thought I'd update you real quick on some of the next steps. We're taking
We're in the process now forming a committee that's going to operate a special fund that we're going to establish through maids
We're working with the sister organization and we're working with private investors and we're putting up our own funds
We are going to begin the process of identifying
Lots
Delapidated homes that could be bought either rehab torn down in new homes put on those locations
And we're also in the process of identifying acreage that we can buy in develop homes
The problem is to talk about repeatedly
We've studied it. We've talked about it now it's time to do something and
We feel like it's up to us to get the process going. We hope that once we get started
We also have some private investors that have contributed some funds to this
That it will spur other development within the community and we can begin the massive shortage we have in housing at all levels
So I just wanted to update you on that also encourage you that if you want to be a part of that process on that committee
Or if you would like to nominate someone to be on that committee, please do so, sooner or
the better, because I'd like to get the ball rolling by the first of June.
So, I just wanted to update you on that process.
The second thing I want to let you know is, the city of Miami approved giving $15,000 for the
housing study.
Part of that was a deal that the MIDA would sell property in the industrial park to
have a population of pipe company.
That process started in November of last year.
We just signed the contracts last week.
So that process is moving forward.
That deal is expected to close before, on or before July 8th.
And so we hope that Felicity will start construction shortly thereafter on their new plant
here in Miami.
So it's welcome news.
We help the local business expand.
Not only expand, but to start a new production of facility, so that's very encouraging.
Other news related to the industrial park, we have a 22.5-acre site that currently we have
four different people businesses looking to purchase.
And so my goal is hopefully within the next month or two we'll be able to come back and let you
know some other updates of what's happening in the industrial park, but positive things are
happening there and so we're excited and encouraged by that.
In the final thing I'm going to talk about, and I'm actually going to just present this
to Mayor Parker.
The Miami Air Economic Development Service stands behind the city of Miami, and it's ongoing
at first to bring about a resolution to the flooding that have plagues Miami and Ottawa County.
And to that we have drafted a letter of support that will be going out to FURK tomorrow, but
I want to present you Mayor Flick-A-Coffee.
This affects all of us at all levels.
It affects economic development, it affects our ability to build and grow from a housing
standpoint, plan and means, resolution to this issue, and hopefully miss them all with the
other letters in the city of selected, it has an impact on the federal level and we can get resolution.
for the quick, if you don't mind, but that's asking me to read it.
Okay.
So there's Secretary Reese, the Miami Air Economic Development Service
Incorporated, supports the city of Miami, Oklahoma, and this desire
to address the severe recurring flooding that has played our communities
and federally recognized tribes for many years.
Regarding the licensure issue that is currently before the Federal Energy
Regulatory Commission concerning the operation of the
Pensacola Dam by the Grand River Dam Authority, we respectfully request
that FERC convene all stakeholders to craft the plan to mitigate,
to mitigate the impact of repeated flooding on the health and safety
of our residents and our economy.
As an economic development agency,
maids recognizes the impacts of flooding,
each stand for beyond physical property damage, business closures,
infrastructure, strain, and public health risk creating,
creating, creating, creating effects that undermine our
region's economic stability and quality of life.
The expansion of the flood plain, because of years of catastrophic flooding,
has left our communities with limited opportunities for future economic growth.
We simply request FERC use this relicensure opportunity to help protect our
communities and encourage all parties to work together, work toward the
goal of accountability, transparency, and teamwork.
Thank you for your time and consideration regarding this matter.
Sign by our Board Chairman Cameron Wilkins and myself.
Happy to answer any other questions you may have.
Thank you, Chair.
Thank you.
Councillor, I bring you guys the MOU between the city and the Auto County Fairboard
for the year's 2526.
Nothing's changed with just updated debates, and we look through your approval.
Thank you.
Thanks.
So, yeah, if you guys remember, we replaced the tariff at Stadium, and now we have roughly
63,000 square feet at that tariff at the parks barn, we're hoping that Council will approve
us to serve plus. There's many different ways to serve plus it. Actually, Crystal Park will put you on the spot for just a second.
She had an idea that come up just the other day that I think might be the best way to approach it as far as the circle.
So, what would it be in the city of Austria as well?
We're just going to spend a bit of experience with people that don't like it.
We've had a lot of showcat people that come up to us.
We want it for you.
Yeah, we've had a circle.
Just somebody's reached out to you Kevin, right?
They wanted it all.
It's up to them to pick it up, but in all it's been long.
Yeah.
They have to have some kind of special insurance to pick it up for a property.
Are they going to bring your own machinery?
Yeah.
It's basically to make some kind of special rights but for...
Then we need to have first that they have at least liability insurance, co-harmonics, co-harmonics, co-harmonics, co-harmonics, co-harmonics, co-harmonics, co-harmonics, co-harmonics, co-harmonics, co-harmonics, co-harmonics, co-harmonics, co-harmonics and co-harmonics.
That's all I have for this show.
So, just for the record and you go in the minutes, we talked about the money that we sold.
They would go to parks and the street department, say, you know, the street department for obviously street stuff.
The parks, sports for, you know, those kind of things.
So, are you looking for a motion to approve what we have talked about?
Yes.
I make a motion.
Hi.
What have an discussion about collection regarding the imposed memorandum of understanding,
for my own approach to go to the least dual-volved sports conflict?
It's not really a lease.
Um...
I don't think right, you know, these are time to leave.
We need to email you at the same time.
Yeah.
So this is an MOU.
As we know, my part of the school has pretty much
a brand that is for Joe Pollock.
The city has dabbled with it with a few revenue tournaments, but not much.
But basically, they've shown interest to basically have exclusive to it,
which they would take care of everything, all the maintenance, all the insurance,
from the top to bottom.
So it's meeting with staff or with the administration at the school district.
They seem to think this will be the best route for them too, as well.
Just because of the usage that they have, and not as much.
They will set aside a few dates for the city if we do produce a revenue event at that place for us to use it.
It seems like this is probably the best route for everybody involved.
The city still owns it.
They will just pay a rental payment, so to speak, every year.
And then take care of all the maintenance and all the insurance and all the utility bills.
And everything goes along with it.
So I guess I'll look confused because a year maybe maybe two years ago.
What the school came to this and all the time.
You didn't want that.
No, that was you didn't apologize for now.
That the school district right now does not have a property that would never house a baseball field right now.
When I read this earlier, Chuck said we maintain the light.
So we'll still be responsible for our placing that.
So pretty much the handle all the maintenance on everything other than the lights and the scoreboard.
Yeah, you might help me with that.
I'm not a hundred percent sure on the lights.
Yeah.
We worked on this last couple of years.
This just clears up.
You essentially responsible for the responsibilities of the lost.
He's always been on the same maintenance.
Years.
And now the school.
Share and the polls were doing exclusively the parking lot.
And then they're paying.
Six.
Six hundred.
Five hundred.
Six thousand a year that we will use for.
Up days and things.
We're walking a fine line on the landlord tenant act.
We have to be able to say we have to be able to have guns to put major repairs.
If they.
But structural repairs and such they will do the painting and all.
of that all of that on a maintenance subject to approval by the city, but we will keep that.
I think that's what we said. Keep that 6,000 in a lack of a dedicated fund to be able to do
any major repairs to commence. So put it in the latch hole for what? Yes, I mean, I have to change
about the LED lights, you know, and so the other lights and change the poles. I mean, the poles are a
little suspect of climbing whenever there is a new gift, but yeah. What about, as far as like
monitoring of the maintenance so we have somebody that's going to be looking at it like you know,
the fire on your whatever set. Is that still a set of a U2? Yeah. Nice. I'm going to have were on a
ventricilla.motion to approve. Hi. Hi. Hi. Hi.
We are last year, when I was here, we established a feast schedule for the Miami Reckon
report.
The previous administrations in the past, after attending some OA conferences and talking
with the state and with the FAA, they would like us to bring our rates up to more reasonable
and customer standards.
So I took that before the board, and they did provide a recommendation of increasing the
hang of rent up to 5% across the board.
Also, on the corporate hang of rent, they would like to increase it up to 43 cents of square
foot.
Instead of 25 cents of square foot, that just provides additional income, therefore, the hangers
do need a lot of work.
We understand that, but by raising and by providing this increase, we can use that to help
fund our updates that we are looking to do.
In order to ask the state in the FAA for additional funding, then we have to prove that
we are charging a reasonable rate.
So that's why we are asking for the...
and crisis today. Then we have a new charge that I would like to add. I am being challenged
with providing additional revenue at the airport. I think that we need to incorporate
our community, not just our pilots, so we want the community to feel like they can come
out and join our events. They don't have to be pilots to do so. So I would like to incorporate
some birthday parties for our kids. It will also provide aviation education, hopefully get
them involved and possibly want to be a pilot in the future. So those are some things
that I am really excited about, but that is why I am here to ask for your approval
for these three things. Do we have any data on what the increase in revenue will look
like, what we are making all the resources, what the increase will make? We haven't ran
in that. Our handers will fail. All but two, yes.
We have 24, and then we have 24 tea hangers and we have four twin hangers, which are a little
larger, and then we have four of the private hangers that are four private guests.
In my gandals said, I mean the board voted to increase them by 25%. As you can see on the areas
it's great. So they actually raise an already raised or that's what we are voting on.
Those are the raised amounts, yes. So the hangers, the point hangers, so my private, they were $80
for asking to fund $200. The private ones were one ten. We are asking to raise that up
to one thirty seven fifty, and the twin hangers or the forty by sixies was two ten. We are asking
for twenty five percent increase, which will bring it up to two sixty two fifty.
And as far as the birthday party is up like a two hour thing or four hour thing. So it will be
one hour time block. So, you know, some of the things that we will provide is an aviation
cake. If you know, depending on which package you choose, but I will partner with either Walmart
here locally or Sam's Club to make sure that we get that done. Molland has been kind enough to give
me the name of the bakery department out at the manager out at Walmart. I can see if we can
partner with them to see if possibly we can get this.
same prices that we can and Sam's in Joplin, that way we can keep our money local.
Hello, the idea about the birthday thing, but is that an insurance issue?
So we would, we've already addressed that issue and that they currently do that for Parks and Recreation when they, they rented out.
So we would follow the insurance procedures with risk management that they already currently do with the to the policy.
Okay.
So I will be providing, so I'll be providing entertainment.
So we're going to be doing FAA STEM activities because obviously, you know, you guys already know that I'm a big STEM supporter and I really want to permit aviation as well.
So the FAA already has a whole list of activities broke down by age range that we can follow that I found fascinating.
So I've already got that saved on our server and I'm going through that to, you know, incorporate some of those ideas as well.
And your confidence that it's a $200, the initial $200 package that covers all overheads.
Yes, so we do have aviation things on as far as like the cups in the napkins and things like that.
They do have packages on Amazon where we can actually buy a bulk, which will actually save us money and then.
Like I said for the cake, that's already been included to and it's anywhere from 40 to 60 dollars for the cake depending on what size they choose.
So there we go.
Come on out. I'd love to have you.
My name is on here but Kevin did all this.
Since the senior center is new to us, we didn't have any free schedule.
So we started with memberships and went with everything we thought we would possibly be doing there.
From full-term as to regular classes to group events and running it out.
Kevin did, do the bulk of this a lot of it is off of what the city already does in the other
rental areas. So the one thing we did add was like the exclusive to a group $10 per hour.
That is if a group that currently does something they're during the day does not want anybody new to
join, then they have to pay a $10 an hour fee in order to keep that private.
Anybody have any questions about anything that's on there?
I think much to approve.
Hi. Hi.
The membership for a paid member for a non-member for our clean and volatile but
per day per hour.
So they could have it for the entire day for honor box versus if they're going to be there.
Okay.
So did you say hi? Did you say hi? Yes. Okay.
14. Or that's 25. 25. 25.
That's 25. That's 25. That's 25. That's 25. That's 25. That's 25. That's 25. That's 25. That's 25.
Bill and Taylor was within chapter 24. E-Gilities are equal to.
Great changes.
Division 2, electricity, establishing electric, great schedule.
So this is all we've already approved on the M.A.C.A. side. This is just the actual ordinance on the city side.
Let's try proof.
Hi. Hi.
Hi.
Hi. Hi. Hi. 15. Or in this 2020 by that year for many sections 24 to 60 of the power
purchased power or death.
So this is the same as we did on the M.A.C.A.A. this is just the PPA that we changed our calculation.
Hi. Hi.
16. The clear list of the city fleet equipment and including the packet and the surplus and authorized items to be offered
yourself in auction. So the scrap can destroy your land sign or even the city manager or the
emotional crew. Take it.
Quick. So the list that is in your packet are going to be two hours on a paper.
and we are going to start.
Hi.
17.
The Warden Hall.
Bid for Edward Rock.
The body seat.
I'm going to turn around and pay back.
It's a short and corporate as gifts.
I'm going to talk to you in the future.
I'm going to say.
The red men must have the proof of contact.
Continue to call this mission.
A lot of bars.
I'm trying to knock.
Who should do this is the same?
Yeah.
Thank you.
Hi.
I'm Joe.
18.
I'm called on through Thursday 25.
Guys can't do the same in the.
I'll show you.
I'm going to show you.
Hi.
Joe.
I'm.
Next time.
Hello.
I'm.
Ando.
What is that?
That's hers head.
I want to mention on this one, we also have the
elevator service that goes to Cone.
And then the other one is for the veterinary service,
as those weren't on the MSUI.
So that's the only difference.
Let's see.
Yeah.
Hi.
Hello.
I'm 22.
How do you do business?
There are many.
We're just focusing on this agenda.
We have some.
Hey.
Welcome to the discuss with me.
I had a call from the county treasurer today.
And she wanted to know what the city would do.
As far as so there is.
Hey, we have approximately $19,000 in lanes on.
The county has another now 10, 11,000 except to 31,000 dollars over on it.
It's going to tax sale, June 9, and they will sell it for two terms of the county,
which is $610 and $1,000.
It's not in front of them.
So the Mr. Heifer has well in the page 20,000 right now.
And Tyler and I were talking live.
I mean, we can't, he has 20,000 to pay.
He wanted us to wave the county fees and assessments which we can't do.
So we were talking, why would we not take 20,000 or a lot of cash from the tax sale for $610?
$610?
I emailed the DA who was not the proper person to email, I've learned when the charge room called me,
but she wanted to know what the city council would do.
What's the time?
So we'll take 20,000.
Well, we'll have to take less.
We'll have to take less than 20.
I mean, I thought it is.
It's like we have leans for 20,000.
And if we don't do some happening.
If we don't do any of that, we're going to end up with $631 that we'll get our percentage
of that.
Can I wrap down here?
But will we pause if there's things on the floodplain?
I thought it was personally bit.
I mean, maybe.
I heard from.
So who ends up that property?
So whoever pays $610 for it, if it goes to tax sale.
So it's.
Except between.
Well, we would accept less than 20.
Yeah.
Yes.
And then.
Borderline, you said?
Please, like, it might be in the flood zone.
No, but.
Yes.
My thought is.
That could be a pretty, pretty property.
We may want for that road or something at some point.
I don't think it's ever flooded.
Right there.
I don't think that.
It's probably been real close.
But I don't think it's ever flooded.
It's going to be recognized as in the flood zone.
Yeah.
Yeah, they're talking about it.
It is a little bug bug.
We are there and it is, I spoon it up.
Two eight strong voice.
Lost the big 20 grand for it.
People pay 20 grand for it.
I'm absent information.
He really has to.
He will.
And so I think this is joint only with his wife.
And he doesn't want his wife knowing that it's about to be sold a textile.
And that's what I was trying to do.
She probably is up now.
There's just changed hybrid.
Yes.
Okay.
So.
20,000 dollars.
This split between us and the county.
That was split.
Well, that's what she wants to know.
What will be sitting there?
Well, what will be the county?
It was us 20.
It was them 10.
Then.
It was us.
Two thirds.
So.
Two thirds and 20,000.
I can offer it.
I mean, that seems fair to me.
That's not fair.
And I don't think we'd afford it.
Or everybody else.
I mean, this is more of a bit more beginning.
It was going to go the South.
Yeah.
It's more than six hundred and ten dollars.
I mean, that's fair.
Be those those.
Those in.
So offered.
Two thirds.
And a piece.
I would order one third.
We can do that.
One third, and then we get the two.
Okay.
Does that seem fair to me?
No.
I mean.
After we all were us to make that all.
You want to do that.
I'm going to do that here.
motion to authorize motion second
So what would that number come out to be
It's a 6,600 60 cc to dollars for just 3,033 dollars
3rd and 2 third of 10,000
Oh, where did I get 10,000?
That's what they all look at me
I did
We're not going to be on board all the way
So how are you still?
Hi
You need to change that as well
We're not going to be on it
I'll throw it in 40 cents
Yeah
You throw it in this dog
You say hi
Hi
What's up
I'm Darren Lord
I'm going to close
So that just to be clear, I'm going to offer that the county takes $6,667 and we take $13,330.
Yes.
And then, just out of what we do that, or does that go back to the first echo?
Yeah, I got on the general fund that covered the leans.
It's not the budget for next year.
Well, people are going to ask them.
No, so that's all right.
All right.
Anything else for you?
But it does bring up a good point, though.
I mean, we're running into this more and more, because we're going after these leans now.
That's good.
That's excellent.
Well, I think that the other county, they owe us.
I mean, I think that's a pretty good split.
The way you should go by.
Oh, depends on one of the others, what the end of all the county.
Right.
Well, I mean, even if it's a bit swapped, the other county,
the other county, though, the end.
Then, I mean, we'd better.
We think the numbers will go to the lighter, right?
Well, I'm lighter on, or a Beckman or a demolition or whatever.
That's money that we've expended for that service.
So when we collect that, it would go in the marginal fund.
So I guess what happens with the property, if we, though, for this amount,
to keep the property still going to sell.
We were really starlings in there.
He would keep property.
We didn't allow him to dispense.
We talked about the amount right now.
We're planning on things that we should be talking about right now.
Okay.
23 staff reports.
24.
We can read out there.
Everybody got a chance to meet the new police chief and try to grow.
Congratulations.
Have a good future coming out tonight.
Welcome.
Welcome, Chief Town.
I don't know if people are excited.
And then those, you are, too.
Great enough.
Welcome to your new job.
Well, if you got it done, it's great.
I appreciate the effort.
You guys.
If you got it, put in early on and get a ground running.
And make notice from me.
Appreciate it.
We're really going on a great team there.
So I appreciate everybody's efforts.
1, 5.
I'm led everybody know that you know the PCA access paid off so that's good
I'm going to talk about the MSGA but case of basically is not tuning in. I'm trying to
want to remind everybody of the Main Street dinner. You know tickets to $100 for two people
or $50 for singles. I mean it levels this catering it and then they have live entertainment
by local artist Trent and Tanner and they don't have a live auction.
Yeah and she needs help. So, and I guess...
I think she's requested, I think she's requested, and I think she's requested the council
attend and help the auctioneer accept the bid from the crowd to get us involved.
So if you can be there, you'd like to be there to help.
I'll be there.
We don't want any of the ties over there.
And the last thing I have is it's something I'm kind of excited about because when I get a lot of
here about a lot of the community is we've started property hearings to start dimming homes again
that need to be dimmed. So I mean I'm sure the board will hear some calls from that but I know
Mr. Travis Chris everybody's worked very hard on this getting some one property.
They get lots of calls about on CVones.
They showed up and they pulled out a six year old pro bank that was started and never finished.
So I thought we could just intervene in the pro bank.
Well, when I had it to dimmed it, I thought we could just intervene in the pro bank
that I would check with the pro bank while you're inbound out that we need to serve the personal representatives.
So we're going to start it.
Just out of the assignments of caution because you do process that it's cool.
And I have proper notice and ability to be heard.
Although the first representative was there so she has actual notice.
So I'm not calling the process that we started over.
They're just working hard to clean up my notes, so something like that. Now we get a lot of calls about stuff.
No one's out there.
I heard the North West at one house.
The one house in the North West by the old Marvin's beside it.
Bebe Streep.
We can send the list in the list.
Let's send the list to all the board.
Yeah.
We've been about 900 block of being Northwest.
I thought it was.
Just playing it on here.
Somebody's sleeping in line.
It's right beside the old Marvin's, right behind it.
Right behind that part.
Yeah, it's fine.
It's the wind.
It's from all out of it.
It's everything.
Yeah.
It's probably like 30.
So the one's got to prove one time frame on demo start.
There's something we wanted to talk to the board about.
Because we budget so much money every year for the demo fund.
maybe taking some of that money and having
city crews do it, but then using that money for
street or for electric project if the electric
group does or something.
And right behind my house, I know there's people
squatting in it.
It's burnt.
Shooter.
So it burns.
It burns.
It's the old brat in the house.
What is this like?
Is your microphone away in that way?
Guys, like I act like I'm the only one
in the way I'll script out here.
Yeah.
Guys, they're so far off script.
We're not even having a council meeting
in the height.
Please, please.
I mean, now that you reconvene,
I will be reconvene from Cal State
where you reconvene is that for the performance.
For the executive session,
after the completion of the greater meeting.
I'll be back then.
Yeah.
On my side.
Yes.